hey what's up guys how are you guys
doing and let's say no see guys oh my
gosh I'm so sorry guys did I haven't
done any luck or videos or even live
streaming so sorry guys sorry Nick
the vector violin am I gonna go okay
today guys as you can see on the title
along in Amana and I going at it today
is Error unbox unboxing my unboxing is
review review so yes cuz I came across
and this product well you know how my
god I know I don't want to cheese
so here it is Tokyo white this is the
Tokyo white face and body Seoul and
Tokyo white buddy LaShawn yeah I'm super
excited because it never come anatomic
in a review about a open body lotion I
mean I'm a beauty stuff are you super
excited about to do this yeah and to
introduce you guys
the take your white faces body something
funny little okay so let's talk
about free fume packaging yeah oh my
gosh there's such a beauty guru I give
you a package in yeah as you can see on
the packaging that alone is a patient
it's a face and body so super simple but
yet elegant like I'm Gandini bonaga
super easy and super bundle and about
white with the flower Mart the Sakura
mark on it
I really like the packaging how they
made the packaging super than men and
pasilla do not accept if seal is broken
making a person
it's a child so I don't talk you're
white because it's a new brand
now go feet back on release by padding
the bus below oh wait before disclaimer
I'm gonna bag buckle my new bucket but
bageno go whitening soap like a tsunami
you don't need any whitening Sophie my
bank dad but yes I don't need any white
guys is you landed on another solar at
on vitamin C and E I need my antioxidant
and my vitamin C and a healthy time you
forever and ever yay oh my guess so
epic I think those soaps it has
glutathione vitamin C and E with natural
whitening ingredients and antioxidants
oh my god and for for wider and
moisturize skin challenge so urine and
at an apartment and Adina body toe is
facing body salsa which means it's two
and one
the best on San Fran alibi
well it is a paid finishes arm buddy
actually I've been using this so and the
body lotion for weeks now I'm one member
or for weeks now
then I really really like it I guess a
person person a super lasagna you smell
yeah both both pneumonia
Superman is super into because I'm a
commodity
Superboy next day mainly other super
cell phone I encountered before this
like cuz I buy I'm going like well well
some of the people will think that it's
a good smell but for me and I like it
you know me good my ego gets it that
like offices my smell guys can yeah I'm
a bug along with I don't even like video
law for today pet him open in the hole
gonna knock a little bit oh my god you
must do the dynamic pop Obama power
gonna know I never see ya a chakra
Napolitan kazehaya is super Bullinger as
in grabbing bullying never my goal
attempt at Kabul anyhow a cover to the
head like be some any lung it somehow
hakuna or I know I don't I hit them my
Bouboulina to like a wave pattern soon
it you know but I'm still motile I got a
vitamin C and E at a Austin oh my god
this is getting ugly view but I know one
another Unicode Nia Tokyo white is a
premium face and body soap that contains
highly effective whitening ingredients
of glutathione and vitamin C and turns
my natural whiteners from our burn our
butene and grapeseed extract that helps
whiten skin natural
Wow it also has vitamin e to promote
skin hydration and deep moist residence
for soap and smooth whiten skin below
let's go using the quality standards of
Japanese skin whitening technology Tokyo
white will help you achieve naturally
petal soft cherry blossoms booth pinkish
white Japanese skin glow gestapo you're
stopping yunyoung natural in a pinkish
white skin I would love that for myself
because I was a yellow skin I have this
local yarn or ingredients get an another
ingredients ingredients has a Coco's
nucifera coconut oil level then aqua
sodium hydroxide oh my god I can't read
my gosh fragrance our bikini which is
for being a fara 15 extra sodium so cool
there we are exiting search in allah
alone you come back occur in the
nobuseri my ingredients sometimes good
day some days many analogous Adama
delicate and ingredients my chemicals
Nepali my property which costs noon skin
not in Madrid a visual Nutella card is a
skin that they are you guys bug movie we
didn't gonna support one or the new my
ingredient is not check minima
there's something to become a minor you
got ingredients you my anonymity my and
a bleach you got any kind of okay so my
gun and Jessica so in Italian okay yeah
but this one took your wife doesn't
contain any any of that chemical things
it's all natural ingredients okay open
and a pina colada
open up whenever let's open it up open
up anything okay set up mean yeah look
at that
Herbert when I searched about this one
it's just that it it's all under the
birthday it's this thing is called in
our department
Phillipa peridot you a movie is Hindi
Hindi Takumi no no run away don't run
away oh boy did I open it guys look
can I be like I'm but when you're gonna
advocating to eat the balance yourself
by donating your bottom bottom plastic
knees I'm burn with anger okay open open
at it let's go
Graham bonnet on I got super I know I
know India Canada beard I hear you my
little sister like stop it inside let me
smell it okay okay I didn't gonna take
an element away
next is date and I gave I'm when you're
like okay I didn't you super nephew
but when I'm in talega I'm a smell free
then you be nun gets happen on top
attitude I smell good
did you so much dr. white on Apple
ending up in Iquitos in you know my
since a boom with nothing
this is how you deep you it okay
nothing okay
I don't know and then well thank you my
my Sakura Sakura Marsha to take this
graphic you
and I mean I super high so what am i
evil so no money go to me okay okay
next Amanda talked about the body lotion
oh my gosh this is really my fave my
favorite body lotion oh my god may
actually may open one knife a ton
did you movie kita is better than don't
shop mr. ma to be too mean I can be
taken with a so you're super love my
love put on body lotion is just super
like Krabby I'm wiping on my gosh for we
got a dead body lotion smell of course
cuz I'm out oh my gosh okay super
happiness indeed I've repaid in the know
Manuel de Mena and I'm your new house
mahabhava so mocha and I mean yesterday
guitar to 250 and Elden it's pumping
selpa oh my god I love it I really
really love this good IV InnoDB do not
know I've got to look at the Buffalo
shelter coming to commit sorrento grab
it so I don't handed in immense body
lotion at all is same nominee
images or it contains same thing like go
to the tyrants like meaty and in with
natural wiping ingredients and
antioxidants in your mansion the best
i'ma tell you who got me to my shambles
compatible a legacy a partner in crime
yes it's a natural whitening and
moisturizing body lotion okay numbers
including heat oh my instant launch
haven't in a character I are holding the
you know Papa saia's skin cause skin
color is not even so as la luna and Nick
Pappas Abajo but alas okay the yellow
fat hippo so and super dry skin Polacco
guys important Andean about meeting your
best super dry skin the papaya something
Misaka time skin nothing but super
dragon animal argon a lag on total life
beside Nadi Simba same nominated as
cinema and even a so let's record it
also direction yeah apply evenly all
over your body after taking a bath for
best results use with Tokyo white
natural why kini and moisturizes face
and body so the bass Oh every day I use
this every morning every night but my
sulo
after taking about or morning Shekinah
and a beloved person on a first
impression phenom very good the
sacristans below this is like a
packaging annular anger and of the best
i love has immediate super the white and
pink on the nation that's best
it's a brand-new release took your why
go check them out guys they have
Facebook then I will link all their
website and Facebook are older social
media down below so you could check me
it up guys okay guys that's it for today
[Music]
I'm so sorry guess baggala Alcala
telegram a vlog and video and at the
same time I want to do this stuff like
reviewing unboxing I really love it so
thank you so much guys for watching if
you like this kind of video please give
me a big thumbs up and if you haven't
joined my family club I have a family up
now guys Nami piglets please join me
family clubs searches on Facebook's Nami
piglets official okay thank you
oh and follow me around follow me on my
Instagram my facebook Nami
Illuma Nami onuma yay okay thanks so
much guys for watching I'll see you guys
on my next video or blog or I to know
[Music]
[Applause]